在本节课中，你将学习如何通过
In this lesson, you'll learn how to use Claude
GitHub 集成在终端之外使用 Claude Code。
Code outside of the terminal with a GitHub integration.
你将看到如何设置 Claude Code
You'll see how to set up Claude Code
来审查拉取请求并修复 GitHub 中的问题。
to review pull requests and fix issues in GitHub.
随后，你还将学习如何通过
You'll then learn how to execute code before
Claude Code 钩子在调用工具前后执行代码。让我们开始吧。
and after using tools through Claude Code hooks. Let's dive in.
我们在上一节结束时将 worktrees 合并到了一起，
We left off in the last section merging our wortrees together,
但我们忘记让 Claude 移除这些 worktrees 了。
but we forgot to ask Claude to remove those worktrees.
所以我们要重新回到 Claude。所以
So we're going to hop back into Claude. So
我将传入 resume 标志
I'm going to go and pass in the resume flag
以回到之前
to go back to a previous
关于 worktrees 的对话中。
conversation that I had with my worktrees.
在这个特定的对话中，我们现在可以
In this particular conversation, we can now
回到之前的位置
go back to where we were before
并完成移除 worktrees 的工作。
and finish up with removing our worktrees.
让我们要求 Claude，移除 .trees 文件夹
So let's ask Claude, remove the .trees folder
及其包含的 worktrees，完成后
and the underlying worktrees, and once you're done,
将代码推送到 GitHub。所以
push this code to GitHub. So
让我们给 Claude Code
let's go ahead and give Claude Code
一点时间来运行必要的 git 命令
a second to run the necessary git commands
以移除文件夹并把合并后的代码
to remove that folder and then pushed our merge code
推送到 GitHub。我们要授予 Claude Code 权限来
to GitHub. We'll go ahead and give Claude Code access to
查看底层的 worktrees，这样我们不仅能
see the underlying worktrees so that we not only
移除 worktrees，
remove the worktrees,
还能删除对应的分支。
but also delete the corresponding branches.
我们将移除这些特定的 trees。
We'll go ahead and remove these particular trees.
现在移除目录并删除底层的分支。
now remove the directory and then remove the underlying branches.
既然已经完成了，让我们
Now that we've done that, let's go ahead
确认一切符合预期，很好。
make sure that worked as expected, which is good.
该文件夹已不在。而且
we don't have that folder. And
现在，让我们把代码推送到 GitHub。
now, let's push this code to GitHub.
我们确认想要
We'll confirm that we want to
运行 git push origin main 命令
run the git push origin main command
看来代码已经推送到 GitHub 了。
and it looks like our code is pushed to GitHub.
提交并推送代码后，
Now that we've committed and pushed our code to GitHub,
让我们开始安装 Claude Code 附带的 GitHub 集成。
let's start installing the GitHub integration that comes with Claude Code.
我将使用 /install-GitHub-app 命令。
I'll do that using the /install-GitHub-app command.
在这里你可能会看到需要
Here you might see that you need to
使用命令行界面进行额外的身份验证。
include additional authentication using the command line interface.
如果你看到这些设置指令，请务必遵循。
So if you see those setup instructions, make sure to follow them.
我们现在可以为正在处理的当前仓库
We'll now be able to install the GitHub
安装 GitHub app。
app for the current repository that we're working in.
让我们开始操作。
So let's go ahead and do
这会打开浏览器。
that. This will open up the browser.
如果我还没有配置过，
And if I have not yet configured
会有安装选项。
this, I'll have the option to install.
这项集成允许我们在
What this integration allows us to do is use Claude Code
拉取请求和议题中使用 Claude Code
in pull requests and issues
以响应反馈、修复错误、
to respond to feedback, fix errors,
修改代码等等。
modify code, and much more.
为了实现这些功能，
In order for this functionality to exist,
它是构建在 Claude Code 附带的
it's built on top of the software development kit
软件开发工具包之上的。这个 SDK 允许你
that comes with Claude Code. This SDK allows you
在终端界面之外
to use Claude Code outside
使用 Claude Code。让我们回到终端。
of the terminal interface. So let's head back to the terminal.
指定我们想要安装的工作流。
specify the workflows we want to install.
这些工作流允许在议题中标记 Claude
These workflows allow for tagging Claude in issues
并利用 Claude 自动审查 PR 中的代码。
and using Claude to automatically review code in our pull requests.
我们两个都安装。我们将创建一个长效令牌。
Let's install both. We'll create a long-lived token.
在这里我们需要与 Claude 进行授权和身份验证。
and here we'll have to authorize and authenticate with Claude.
完成后回到终端，
Once that's done, we can head back
我们会看到它正在创建仓库信息，
and we'll see that it's creating the repository information,
设置所需的额外信息，
setting up any additional information I need,
并直接把我带回 GitHub
and sending me right back to GitHub
去开启一个拉取请求。
to open a pull request.
其中包含了刚才所做的更改。
with the changes that had been made.
我们可以看到，自动生成的
We can see here automatically,
拉取请求允许 GitHub Actions
this pull request allows for GitHub Actions
进行错误修复、编写测试和代码审查。
to enable bug fixes, writing tests and code reviews.
我们可以根据喜好更改这些，
We can change this if we like,
也可以直接使用默认信息
or we can go ahead and create a pull request
创建拉取请求。在 PR 中，我们可以看到
with the default information. In this pull request, we can see
不仅创建了一个
that not only have we created
让 Claude 运行的 YAML 文件，
a YAML file for Claude to operate,
还有一个用于代码审查的文件。
we also have one for code reviews.
在这里我们可以看到，
Here we can see out of the
它提供了一些非常合理的默认设置。我们可以
box, we have some pretty sane defaults. We can filter
按作者过滤，也可以指定运行环境。
by authors, we can specify what this is running on.
但开箱即用的功能
But out of the box, we get
已经非常丰富了。
quite a bit of really nice functionality.
如果你想修改代码审查中的
If you'd like to modify the prompt
提示词，可以在这里操作。
that you have in your code review, you can do that here.
由于这是一个由 git 追踪的文件，
And since this is a file that is tracked by git,
你可以根据需要不断对其进行编辑。
you can constantly edit this if you need.
我现在要将其合并，
I'm going to go ahead now and merge this in,
以便开始在 GitHub 中使用 Claude Code。
so we can start using Claude Code in GitHub.
我们可以直接看到
We can go ahead and see right out of
一个 Claude GitHub Action 已经启动了。
the box that a Claude GitHub action has actually started.
这就是我们在未来的
This is what we're going to see out
拉取请求中会看到的。
of the box in our future pull requests.
它会读取并分析文件、检查代码质量、
It's going to read and analyze files, check code quality,
识别安全隐患。现在
identify security considerations, and out of the box,
我们有了一个新队友 Claude，
we now have a new teammate, Claude,
来检查我们
to check the work that we
和其他团队成员的工作。
and our other team members are doing.
这有时需要一点
This sometimes takes a little bit of
时间启动，但一旦完成，
time to start, but once this has finished,
我们会从 Claude 那里得到详细评估，
we'll get some detailed assessments from Claude,
并在准备好时
and we'll be able to merge in the pull request
合并 PR。审查看起来已经完成了，
when we're ready. So it looks like the review is done,
根据我们给它的提示词，我们可以指定
and depending on the prompt that we give it, we can specify
想要的信息深度。
how much depth and information we want here.
我们能看到哪些地方做得好，
We see some things that are working well,
以及一些可能需要的
maybe some considerations that we
考虑因素。如果看起来不错，
you may need. And if this looks good to us,
我们就可以合并该 PR。现在
we can merge in that pull request. Now
我们将看到，
we're going to see out of the box,
在未来的 PR 中，Claude 都会帮助审查代码。
in future pull requests, Claude will help review our code.
当人类可能遗漏某些细节
This is really helpful when humans might miss certain things
而你需要额外一步来检查
and you need an extra step to check
一切是否按预期工作时，这非常有用。
that what you have is working as expected.
假设出现了一个议题出现的情况。
Let's imagine there's a situation where an issue comes up.
团队中的某人决定添加一个新议题。
Someone on our team decides to add a new issue.
我们可以在 GitHub 中操作，
We could do this in GitHub, we
甚至可以在 Claude Code 中操作。
could even do this in Claude Code.
你可能已经注意到，随着我们在这个应用上
As you might have noticed, as we kept building on
不断构建，我们看到了一个
top of this application, we started to see a new
新添加的页眉。这个新页眉
new header that was added. This new header
看起来可能还不错，但也许我们
might look kind of nice, but maybe we
想恢复到之前的状态。
want to revert to what we had previously.
所以让我们添加一个议题，
So let's add an issue and
看看 Claude 能否帮上忙。
see if Claude can help us out.
想象一下我们这里有一个议题。
You can imagine we have an issue here.
应用添加了一个新页眉，
The application has a new header that was added,
让我们恢复到旧页眉。
Let's go back to the old one.
确保保留主题切换按钮，但
Make sure to keep the toggle theme but just
让页眉看起来像以前一样。我们还会指定：
make the header look like what it was before. We'll also specify,
确保移除 Course Materials Assistant 页眉。
make sure to remove the Course Materials Assistant header.
移除子页眉。
Remove the subheader.
移除询问问题的部分，然后移除
around ask questions, and then remove the
子页眉下方的水平线。
horizontal row below the subheader.
创建议题后，
Now that we created this issue,
我们可以指派某人去处理它。
we could assign someone to tackle it.
但为什么不直接请 Claude 帮忙呢？
But why don't we just ask Claude to help us out?
“Claude，你能帮我修复这个吗？”标记 Claude 后，
Claude, can you fix this for me? Once we tag in Claude,
我们要给 Claude 一点时间
we're going to start to give Claude a little bit of time
来修复这个问题。
to fix the issue at hand.
当 Claude 修复好该议题后，
When Claude has fixed that issue,
它应该能够生成一个拉取请求
it should be able to generate a pull request
来修复这个特定问题。所以
to fix that particular one. So
让我们给 Claude 的
let's give Claude a little bit of
Action 一点运行时间。在这里
time to find that action. Here we're
我们可以看到 Claude Code 正在工作，
going to see Claude Code is working,
如果你想查看正在运行的底层作业，
and if we want to see the underlying job that's run,
也可以点击查看。所以
we can go ahead and do that. So
让我们给 Claude 一点时间，
let's give Claude a little bit of time
看看它能做出什么。
and see what it can come up with.
你所看到的界面会感觉非常熟悉，
What you're seeing is going to look very familiar
就像我们在命令行中看到的一样。
to what we saw in the command line.
分析结构、移除页眉。
Analyze the structure, remove the header.
在这里，我甚至可以根据需要选择优先级。
And here, I can even choose what to prioritize if I'd like.
你在终端之外
But what you're seeing here is the same
看到的是同样的事情。
thing we saw just outside of the
我们不仅可以利用 Claude
terminal. Not only can we use Claude
处理议题和 PR，
to tackle issues and pull requests,
还可以像之前那样利用它审查代码。
we can also use Claude to review code as we saw before.
当我们开始查看它的计划时，会注意到
As we start to see its plan, we'll notice
正在进行的更改、
what the changes are that are being
在代码库中提议的位置，
made, where in the codebase it's proposing things,
看到 PR 时，我们可以看到
and as we see the pull request, we can start to
背后的一些思考和逻辑。
see some of the thinking and logic behind what's being done.
看来这个任务并不难，
Seems like this one isn't too tough,
它会遵循这些步骤：
so it's going to follow these steps,
测试更改、提交并推送。
test the changes, commit and push those.
它现在已经完成了必要的提交。
It's now made the commit necessary.
我们可以看到底层的描述信息。
We can see the underlying description here.
如果我们愿意，可以创建这个 PR，
If we'd like, we can create this pull request,
或者让 Claude 帮我们完成所有工作。
or we can just have Claude do all that work for us.
当我们创建拉取请求时。
When we create the pull request.
我们能看到提交中生成的具体内容。
We see exactly what was generated in the commit.
现在让我们去看看 Claude 做了什么。
And now, let's go take a look and see what Claude did.
我们可以查看更改过的底层文件。
We can take a look at the underlying files that we changed.
这里改动不大，我们可以将其合并。
There wasn't too much here. We can merge this in.
正如之前看到的，Claude 还会花时间
As we saw before, Claude's also going to take
审查它自己写的代码。
some time and review the code that Claude wrote.
这其实很有帮助，因为
And this can actually be quite helpful because
尽管我们信任 Claude，
as much as we want to trust Claude,
但让另一个 Claude 双重检查它的工作总是好的。
it's nice to have another Claude double checking its work.
看来 Claude Code
So it looks like Claude Code
已经批准了这个任务。
has approved the task I have here.
让我们合并它。然后回到终端，
Let's merge this in. And then we'll head back to the terminal
并确保拉取下我们所做的更改。
and make sure to pull down the changes. is that we have.
我切换到 VS Code，拉取更改。
So I'll head over to VS Code, pull down the changes.
让我们看看前端是否变好了一些。
And let's see if our front end looks any better.
大功告成。页眉
And there we have it. The header
移除了，水平线也移除了。
is taken out, the horizontal rows taken out.
我们可能想把那条
We might want to bring back that
水平线带回来，或者移到别的地方。
horizontal row or move this to another place.
但现在我们知道该怎么做了，
But now we know how to do it,
不仅在终端，在 GitHub 中也能实现。
not only in the terminal, but also in GitHub.
我最后想展示的一项功能
One more piece of functionality that I want
是最近发布的：
to show is something that was recently released,
向 Claude Code 添加
which is the ability to add
所谓“钩子”的能力。
what's called a hook to Claude Code.
如果你熟悉钩子的概念，
If you're familiar here with this idea of
这会让你感觉非常熟悉。
hooks. This is going to feel very similar.
基本思想是，当 Claude Code 执行不同操作时，
The idea is that as we have different operations in Claude Code,
比如执行工具或工具执行后发生某些事，
like executing a tool or something happening after a tool,
我们可以在其生命周期的任何
we can inject specific code to run at any
时间点注入特定代码来运行。
point in the life cycle of Claude Code's operation.
让我展示一下我的
Let me show you what I mean
意思。回到 VS code，我
by that. Back in VS code, I'm going
再次进入 Claude。而且
to hop in back to Claude again. And
虽然我们可以手动修改，但我
while we can make these changes manually, I
更想向你展示我们拥有的编辑器。
want to show you the editor that we have.
输入 /hooks。
So I'm going to type in slash hooks.
管理工具事件的配置。
manage configurations for tool events.
你看到的内容可能有点吓人，
What you're seeing might look a little bit scary,
但我们有义务让你知道：
but it's our obligation to let you know.
如果你在运行任意 shell 命令，
If you are running arbitrary shell commands,
必须非常小心你的操作。
you have to be very careful about what you're doing.
我们有许多不同的事件可以运行钩子。
There are quite a few different events that we can run hooks.
在工具执行前，我们甚至可以
Before a tool is executed, we can
阻止该工具执行。
even stop that tool from being executed.
我们可以在工具执行后、发送通知时、
We can do something after, when a notification is sent,
当用户提交提示词、程序停止时，
when the user submits a prompt, when something stops,
甚至在子代理结束
or even before a subagent concludes its
响应前执行操作。因此我们有能力
response. So we have the ability to
以编程方式切入这些事件。
programmatically to tap in to any of these events.
我想展示一个简单的 PostToolUse 钩子示例。
I want to show a simple example with a PostToolUse hook.
首先添加一个匹配器。在这个匹配器中，
Start by adding a matcher. In this matcher,
我可以指定想要
I can specify the tools that I want
运行此钩子的工具。
to be matched for this hook to run.
我将添加一个
I'm going to add a very, very
非常简单的例子。任何时候使用 Read
simple example here. Anytime there is a Read
或者使用 Grep 时，
or anytime there is a Grep,
我都运行一个简单的终端命令。
I'm going to run a simple terminal command.
我要运行的新钩子或命令
The new hook or command I'm
是 say 命令。
going to run is the say command.
say 命令会调用电脑的音频
The say command, runs the computer's audio
并说出你指定的文本。
and a path for what text you'd like it to say.
如果我操作正确，那么在读取了某些内容
So if I've done this correctly, after we have read something
或使用 grep 工具在文件中
or use the grep tool to find something
找到内容后，我们的机器应该会说 all done。
in a file, our machine should say, all done.
我们在项目设置中再次添加它。
Let's add this again in our project settings.
之前提到的 settings.local.json 文件是指定权限的地方。
We mentioned earlier the settings.local.json file where we can specify permissions.
这也是你的钩子存放的地方。
This is also where your hooks live.
在我们的 .claude 文件夹内，
Inside of our .claude,
我们可以看到 settings.local.json，
we can see in our settings.local.json,
不仅有权限设置，
not only do we have our permissions,
还有刚才定义的钩子。
but we now have a hook that we've defined.
PostToolUse 是钩子的名称，
PostToolUse is the name of the hook,
匹配器中指定了（如果不加则应用于所有）。
the matcher, which if you take out will apply to anything.
但在这里是 reading 或 grep，
But here, reading or grep,
完成后运行命令 say 'All done!'。
go run the command say 'All done!' when we're done.
让我们试一下。退出 Claude Code。
Let's try this out. I'm going to quit out of Claude Code.
重新打开它。
I'm going to open it up again.
读取 run.sh 文件的内容。
read the contents of the run.sh file.
这应该会如期使用 read 工具。All done。
This should use the read tool as expected. All done.
完成后，它会通知我们并告诉我们已完成。
And once it's done, it notifies us and tells us all done.
虽然这只是个有趣的小例子，但你可以
Well, this is kind of a fun little example, you can
想象更严肃的场景，比如运行测试或 linter，
imagine executing code like running tests or running linters
或者在不希望使用
or potentially stopping tools from being
某些工具时阻止它们，
used if that's not what we want
甚至让 Claude 在某些事件发生时自我审查。
or even having Claude review itself when certain things happen.
利用钩子可以做很多事情，
There's a lot you can do with
未来还会推出更多功能。
hooks and there's so much more that's coming.
所以请务必查看
So make sure to look at the
文档以了解所有用法。
documentation to see everything you can do.
你甚至可以利用 Claude Code 帮你
And you can always use Claude Code to
编写钩子并进行相应修改。
write hooks for you and modify them accordingly.
在下一节中，我们将探索在 Jupyter notebooks 中使用 Claude Code
In the next section, we'll explore using Claude Code with Jupyter notebooks
来创建可视化、重构代码，并在略有不同的环境中进行操作。
to create visualizations, refactor code, and operate in a slightly different environment.